intaz.tv 2015-02-23

# Privacy Policy | intaz

We comply with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data. We will respond to your request for access to modify or delete your information within ten (10) days.

Other than as described in this Policy, we will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.

Information Collection and Use

Our web site uses forms in which you give us contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can request information. For certain services, we may also request a credit card number, social security number or tax identification number, or other financial information. We will then create an account for you.

We receive and store any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way, including through email, telephone, or other communications with our customer service department.

We use your information to contact you regarding giving you free information on any subject, offering you free service and/or gifts and to promote our products, our web site/s, new services, and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the unsubscribe information given at the end of any email you received.

We may also use your information to present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates. If we collect information from you in connection with a co-branded offer, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies.

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

We use cookies to identify you so you don’t need to login each time you visit our site. They are linked to your account which is associated with the information in your account.

This site also contains links to other web sites. Unfortunately, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control.

Updating Your Information

You may alter your account information or opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners at any time. We have the following option for changing and modifying your account information or contact preferences.

1\. You may send an email to support as given at the bottom of any email you received from us.

Sending Emails

We use emails to communicate with you, to send you free gifts, to send you free services, to promote any products and to send information that you have requested.

The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN’s rules, regulations and policies.

Third Party Service Providers

We may at times provide information about you to third parties to provide various services on our behalf, such as but not limited to processing credit card payments, serving advertisements, conducting contests or surveys, performing analyses of our products or customer demographics, shipping of goods or services, and customer relationship management. We will only share information about you that is necessary for the third party to provide the requested service. These companies are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing or using your personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

In the event that we use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf, these companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gift or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

Supplementation of Information

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third party sources ( e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service). We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

Contests/Surveys

From time-to-time, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If you choose to participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these contests or surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose the requested information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age level – note that you must be 18 or above to enter). We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic, and to personalize our site.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests. When we do, that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask the user for the friend’s name and email address. We will send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit our web site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may request the removal of this information from our database. The procedure is given in the email.

What Happens to my Personal Information if I unsubscribe my Account?

When your account is cancelled by way of unsubscription (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is deleted entirely from our database. But we keep backup copy of database only to retain and use your personally identifiable information if necessary in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

Changes in Our Practices

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our home page, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page, at least thirty (30) days prior to the implementation of the changes.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at the address given at the end of any email you received.
